ovaustralia.com 2017-02-07

# ovaustralia.com

**and all related sites owned, operated or controlled by "OVAUSTRALIA"**

### Information Collection and Use

OVAUSTRALIA is the sole owner of all the information collected on this site. OVAUSTRALIA will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. OVAUSTRALIA collects information from our users at several different points on OVAUSTRALIA website. Personal email addresses are obtained to ease points of communication between clients and the OVAUSTRALIA.

### Order

OVAUSTRALIA request information from the user on order form. Here a user must provide contact and personal information (such as, but not limited to, name and address) and financial information (such as, but not limited to, credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer's orders. If OVAUSTRALIA has trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user. OVAUSTRALIA uses the user's information for other purposes as well. 

### Use of Cookies

OVAUSTRALIA uses cookies to gather and store information. Cookies are pieces of data that a web site transfers to user computer's hard drive solely for record-keeping purposes. Cookies help OVAUSTRALIA make its software more useful by storing information on your preferences. There is nothing unusual about the use of cookies by a web site and they are an industry standard. They do not personally identify you, but they will identify your computer. Your browser is most likely set up to accept cookies, but you can set yours to refuse them. If you do so, you may not be able to take full advantage of OVAUSTRALIA's web site. OVAUSTRALIA is not liable for any failure of your computer due to the use of cookies. 

### Log Files

OVAUSTRALIA use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

### Sharing

OVAUSTRALIA share aggregated demographic information with partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. OVAUSTRALIA use an outside shipping company and a credit card processing company to bill users for services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. OVAUSTRALIA partners with another party to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, OVAUSTRALIA will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that OVAUSTRALIA is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. OVAUSTRALIA encourages users to be aware when they leave this site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by OVAUSTRALIA web site.

### Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time OVAUSTRALIA site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

### Emails

All emails sent to users adhere to the strict requirements of the CAN-SPAM Act. Email addresses are only obtained by a customer freely giving their email address (usually on Step1 or the registration). This registration process is understood by the OVAUSTRALIA as a request for additional information about the service. Once a client has paid for the service, emails are sent to aid in the process of registration, by verifying that information has been correctly entered, photos have been successfully uploaded, and to update the client upon his registration status. Clients may receive offers on different products and services, which usually are related to the service of OVAUSTRALIA . Each time an email is sent, users have the ability to opt-out of the email subscription, by either clicking the 'unsubscribe' link provided at the bottom of each email, or by sending an email, fax or telephone request to the OVAUSTRALIA.

### Telephone number

Telephone numbers are only obtained by a customer freely giving their telephone numbers. Giving the telephone number is understood by the OVAUSTRALIA as a request for additional information about the service. Users have the ability to opt-out of the telephone service, by either clicking the 'unsubscribe' link provided at the bottom of each email, or by sending an email, fax or telephone request to the OVAUSTRALIA Organization. Once a client has paid for the service, the client may receive telephone calls for assisting in the registration process, making sure details are correct, photos are successfully uploaded and updating upon the registration status and additional services. 

### Tell-A-Friend

If a user elects to use OVAUSTRALIA referral service for informing a friend about this site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. OVAUSTRALIA will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. After the first email sent, additional emails will only be sent to the friend, if he chooses to register to the OVAUSTRALIA site of his own accord. The friend may contact OVAUSTRALIA at any time to request the removal of the information from the database. 

### Security

This website takes every precaution to protect users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, the information is protected both online and off-line. When registration form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as the payment reply form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked. 

This is the official OVAUSTRALIA web site, which specializes in the assessing Australian eligibility for aa Skilling Migration Visa for clients all over the world. When registering with the OVAUSTRALIA, users should take precaution that they do not register with any site that pretends to be the OVAUSTRALIA. To verify that a registration is with the OVAUSTRALIA, users should check that at the top of the browser it is written OVAUSTRALIA. 

### Special Offers

OVAUSTRALIA send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users OVAUSTRALIA present the option to not receive these types of communications. 

### Correction/Updating Personal Information:

If a user's personally identifiable information changes, or if a user no longer desires OVAUSTRALIA service, OVAUSTRALIA will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to OVAUSTRALIA . This can usually be done at the member information page or by emailing OVAUSTRALIA Customer Support. 

### Choice/Opt-out

OVAUSTRALIA users have the ability to opt-out of receiving emails from the OVAUSTRALIA. An opt-out request may be sent by email, telephone or fax, or by clicking the link provided at the bottom of each email sent to users. Should a user choose to opt-out of the email subscription, the OVAUSTRALIA will honor the request and will not send additional emails.
